https://unify.com/en/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy eStorePrivacy Policy eStore RMAPublic Key InfrastructuresPrivacy PolicyPrivacy Policy
BCR
Unify is part of Atos Group. Atos is the first IT company to have obtained approval of its Binding Corporate Rules (BCRs) by European data protection authorities both as a data controller and a processor. This approval evidences Atos’ commitment to the protection not only of its own data but also that of its clients: all Atos entities provide a very strong level of protection to personal data, regardless of their location in the world. The BCR are a commitment whereby the companies of the Atos Group undertake to process personal data in accordance with a stringent level of protection to personal data it processes for its own needs (employee data, etc.) but also for the needs of its customers, therefore allowing the free flow of personal data between the companies of the Atos Group.
Personal data
Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (“Data Subject”); an identifiable person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to his physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural or social identity.
Through our Web sites, Unify will not collect any personal data about you (e.g. your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address), unless you voluntarily choose to provide us with it (e.g. by registration, survey), respectively, provide your consent, or unless otherwise permitted by applicable laws and regulations for the protection of your personal data.
You have the right to request access, amendment or erasure of your personal data. To exercise these rights, please complete this online form to contact the Data Protection office.
Unify Commitment to Data Privacy Protection
Protecting the security and privacy of your personal data is important to Unify; therefore, we conduct our business in compliance with applicable laws on data privacy protection and data security. We hope the policy outlined below will help you understand what data Unify may collect, how Unify uses and safeguards that data and with whom we may share it.
Purpose of Use
When you do provide us with personal data, we usually use it to respond to your inquiry, process your order or provide you access to specific information or offers. In order to best respond to your request, we may pass your information to a certified Unify partner. Also, to support our customer relationship with you:
we may store and process personal data and share it with our worldwide affiliates to better understand your business needs and how we can improve our products and services; or
we (or a third party on our behalf) may use personal data to contact you about a Unify offer in support of your business needs or to conduct online surveys to understand better our customers’ needs.
If you choose not to have your personal data used to support our customer relationship (especially direct marketing or market research), we will respect your choice. We do not sell or otherwise market your personal data to third parties, except to Unify affiliates.
Purpose Limitation
Unify will collect, use or disclose personal data supplied by you online only for the purposes disclosed to you, unless the disclosure:
is a use of the personal data for any additional purpose that is directly related to the original purpose for which the personal data was collected,
is necessary to prepare, negotiate and perform a contract with you,
is required by law or the competent governmental or judicial authorities,
is necessary to establish or preserve a legal claim or defense,
is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activities, such as willful attacks on Unify information technology systems.
Communications or Utilization Data
Through your use of telecommunications services to access our Web site, your communications data (e.g. Internet protocol address) or utilization data (e.g. information on the beginning, end and extent of each access, and information on the telecommunications services you accessed) are technically generated and could conceivably relate to personal data. To the extent that there is a compelling necessity, the collection, processing and use of your communications or utilization data will occur and will be performed in accordance with the applicable data privacy protection legal framework.
Non-Personal Data Collected Automatically
When you access our Web sites, we may automatically (i.e., not by registration) collect non-personal data (e.g. type of Internet browser and operating system used, domain name of the Web site from which you came, number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed). We may use this data and share it with our worldwide affiliates to monitor the attractiveness of our Web sites and improve their performance or content.
“Cookies” – Information Stored Automatically on Your Computer
When you view one of our Web sites, we may store some data on your computer in the form of a “cookie” to automatically recognize your PC next time you visit. Cookies can help us in many ways, for example, by allowing us to tailor a Web site to better match your interests or to store your password to save you having to re-enter it each time. If you do not wish to receive cookies, please configure your Internet browser to erase all cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block all cookies or to receive a warning before a cookie is stored.
Children
Unify will not knowingly collect personal data from children without insisting that they seek prior parental consent if required by applicable law. We will only use or disclose personal data about a child to the extent permitted by law, to seek parental consent pursuant to local law and regulations or to protect a child. The definition of “child” or “children” should take into account applicable laws as well as national and regional cultural customs.
Security
To protect your personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss or alteration and against unauthorized disclosure or access, Unify uses technical and organizational security measures.
Links to Other Web Sites
Unify Web sites contain links to other Web sites. Unify is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites.
Questions and Comments
Unify will respond to reasonable requests to review your personal data and to correct, amend or delete any inaccuracies. If you have any questions or comments about the Unify Data Privacy Protection Policy (e.g. to review and update your personal data), please click on “Contact Us” in the upper right-hand corner of this window, and select “About Unify”, “About us – questions about Unify”. As the Internet matures, so will our Data Privacy Protection Policy. We will post changes to our Data Privacy Protection Policy on this page. Please check this page regularly to keep up-to-date.
Use of Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
Read more about Unify’s approach to Data Protection.
Privacy Policy eStorePrivacy Policy eStore
Unify eStore
This Unify eStore Privacy Policy ( “Privacy Policy”) applies to information that Unify, Inc. (“we” or “us”) collect from you as our customer through or in connection with Unify eStore Website (‘Website”).
Protecting the security and privacy of your personal data is important to us, and we conduct our business in compliance with applicable laws on data privacy protection and security. We hope our explanation of our Privacy Policy as outlined below will help you understand what data we may collect and, how we use and safeguard that data.
Data Collection
Personal data. We collect personal data about you which you voluntarily choose to provide us with, including by entering information for Website registration, communicating with us via email, or by giving your explicit consent. This includes information such as your name, address, and phone number.
Non-Personal Data Collected Automatically. When you access our Website, we may automatically receive and store certain types of information, such as the type of Internet browser and operating system used, domain name of the website from which you came, number of visits, and average time spent on the site. We may use this data and share it with our worldwide affiliates to monitor the attractiveness of our websites and improve their performance or content.
“Cookies” – Information Stored Automatically on Your Computer. When you view our Website, we may store some data on your computer in the form of a “cookie” to automatically recognize your computer next time you visit. Cookies can help us in many ways, for example, by allowing us to tailor our Website to better match your interests or to store your password to save you having to re-enter it each time. If you do not wish to receive cookies, please configure your Internet browser to erase all cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block all cookies or to receive a warning before a cookie is stored.
Purpose of Use
When you do provide us with personal data, we usually use it to respond to your inquiry, process your order or provide you access to specific information or offers. We may store and process personal data and share it with our worldwide affiliates to better understand your business needs and how we can improve our products and services. We may also use your information to communicate with you about your account or for security purposes.
We (or a third party on our behalf) may use personal data to contact you about one of our offers that may address your business needs or to conduct online surveys to understand better your needs as a customer. If you choose not to have your personal data used to support our customer relationship (especially direct marketing or market research), we will respect your choice.
Information Sharing
We do disclose information we collect from you when legally permitted, including in the following ways:
We may disclose your information within our company, including to our affiliates.
We may disclose your information with third parties who perform functions on our behalf, such as payment processing or shipping. In this case, disclosure
will be limited to the information necessary for the third party to perform its task.
We may make disclosures necessary to prepare, negotiate and carry out a contract with you.
We may make disclosures required by law or otherwise ordered by the competent governmental or judicial authorities, to establish or preserve a legal claim or defense, or to prevent fraud or other illegal activities.
Security
We use standard technical and organizational security measures to protect your information against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss or alteration and against unauthorized disclosure or access. However, the Internet is not 100% secure, so we cannot promise that your information will be completely safe. Please use caution when using the Internet.
Links to Other Websites
The Website may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.
Questions and Comments
We will respond to reasonable requests to review your personal data and to correct, amend or delete any inaccuracies. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or you wish to change or update your personal data, please contact us by email at global-servicedesk@unify.com.
Use of Google Analytics
Our Website may use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc., or a similar program, which in turn uses cookies to help analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie will be used by Google to evaluate your use of our Website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, but this may in turn prevent you from being able to use the full functionality of this website.
Privacy Policy eStore RMAPrivacy Policy eStore RMA
Unify eStore
This Unify eStore Privacy Policy ( “Privacy Policy”) applies to information that Unify, Inc. (“we” or “us”) collect from you as our customer through or in connection with Unify eStore Website (‘Website”).
Protecting the security and privacy of your personal data is important to us, and we conduct our business in compliance with applicable laws on data privacy protection and security. We hope our explanation of our Privacy Policy as outlined below will help you understand what data we may collect and, how we use and safeguard that data.
Data Collection
Personal data. We collect personal data about you which you voluntarily choose to provide us with, including by entering information for Website registration, communicating with us via email, or by giving your explicit consent. This includes information such as your name, address, and phone number.
Non-Personal Data Collected Automatically. When you access our Website, we may automatically receive and store certain types of information, such as the type of Internet browser and operating system used, domain name of the website from which you came, number of visits, and average time spent on the site. We may use this data and share it with our worldwide affiliates to monitor the attractiveness of our websites and improve their performance or content.
“Cookies” – Information Stored Automatically on Your Computer. When you view our Website, we may store some data on your computer in the form of a “cookie” to automatically recognize your computer next time you visit. Cookies can help us in many ways, for example, by allowing us to tailor our Website to better match your interests or to store your password to save you having to re-enter it each time. If you do not wish to receive cookies, please configure your Internet browser to erase all cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block all cookies or to receive a warning before a cookie is stored.
Purpose of Use
When you do provide us with personal data, we usually use it to respond to your inquiry, process your order or provide you access to specific information or offers. We may store and process personal data and share it with our worldwide affiliates to better understand your business needs and how we can improve our products and services. We may also use your information to communicate with you about your account or for security purposes
We (or a third party on our behalf) may use personal data to contact you about one of our offers that may address your business needs or to conduct online surveys to understand better your needs as a customer. If you choose not to have your personal data used to support our customer relationship (especially direct marketing or market research), we will respect your choice.
Information Sharing
We do disclose information we collect from you when legally permitted, including in the following ways:
We may disclose your information within our company, including to our affiliates.
We may disclose your information with third parties who perform functions on our behalf, such as payment processing or shipping. In this case, disclosure will be limited to the information necessary for the third party to perform its task.
We may make disclosures necessary to prepare, negotiate and carry out a contract with you.
We may make disclosures required by law or otherwise ordered by the competent governmental or judicial authorities, to establish or preserve a legal claim or defense, or to prevent fraud or other illegal activities.
Security
We use standard technical and organizational security measures to protect your information against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss or alteration and against unauthorized disclosure or access. However, the Internet is not 100% secure, so we cannot promise that your information will be completely safe. Please use caution when using the Internet.
Links to Other Websites
The Website may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.
Questions and Comments
We will respond to reasonable requests to review your personal data and to correct, amend or delete any inaccuracies. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or you wish to change or update your personal data, please contact us by email at global-servicedesk@unify.com
Use of Google Analytics
Our Website may use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc., or a similar program, which in turn uses cookies to help analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie will be used by Google to evaluate your use of our Website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, but this may in turn prevent you from being able to use the full functionality of this website.
Public Key InfrastructuresPublic Key Infrastructures
Unify PKI
Here you can download all the Certification Authority certificates made available by “Unify PKI” for installation in your applications (browser, mail clients, …). Click the description of the Certification Authority certificates in the table below. These certificates must be imported in order to enable checking of electronic signatures which were generated using a “Unify PKI” certificate. An import is also necessary if the Outlook or any S/MIME capable mail clients are to be used.
Unify Root CA
Validity: from 25.09.2013 to 25.09.2028
Key length: 2048 Bit RSA
Fingerprint MD5: 7e 42 91 34 fb 51 a3 48 db 63 4c b7 96 66 1b c6
Fingerprint SHA-1: dc 5c 76 22 54 61 87 7a f4 57 8e c6 87 12 d5 3b d4 65 70 e9
Unify Root CA CRL
Validity: for 6 months
Unify User CA
Validity: from 26.09.2013 to 26.09.2023
Key length: 2048 Bit RSA
Fingerprint MD5: 98 a1 64 9c a9 84 09 c8 80 dc d8 00 1e 11 77 50
Fingerprint SHA-1: 3a 02 05 2f 48 c6 b8 69 71 a4 b1 56 78 13 9c 23 15 5d e7 5f
Unify User CA CRL
Validity: for 10 days
Unify Infrastructure CA
Validity: from 30.09.2013 to 30.09.2023
Key length: 2048 Bit RSA
Fingerprint MD5: ff 9c 68 8b 15 93 40 95 66 53 aa 55 25 53 7d f7
Fingerprint SHA-1: 00 33 0b 0c de 78 c9 2a ab a1 ab de 27 07 ab 02 78 dc 15 a5
Unify Infrastructure CA CRL
Validity: for 10 days
Unify PRODUCT CA
Validity: from 30.09.2013 to 30.09.2023
Key length: 2048 Bit RSA
Fingerprint MD5: 4f cd ff a8 a7 2e d4 54 b2 fe ac 2f 33 16 94 45
Fingerprint SHA-1: 4e e8 e0 31 e5 0f fb 72 e5 35 5d a8 e5 23 09 ee 4e 9e d9 a9
Unify PRODUCT CA CRL
Validity: 10 days
Here you can download all the Certification Authority certificates made available by “SEN PKI” for verification of the validity of electronic signatures on E-Mail and documents created with formerly issued certificates. Click the description of the Certification Authority certificates in the table below.
Contact:
For general questions for Unify/SEN PKI certificates please contact it-security@unify.com.
How can I control or delete cookies?
To delete your cookies or change your preferences, please click here.
